

#### How to reach me:

#### Cell:

+90 553 101 91 59

#### Email:

m.farukgul@gmail.com

#### Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/mfg/

#### Github:

github.com/Mastechnology

#### Blog & Site:

mfgstudiosblog.com mastechnology.github.io

## **Professional Skills**

# **Coding Languages:**



## Frameworks/Systems:



## **Personal Skills**

Team working, problem solving, willingness to learn, time management, organized

# **Hobbies**

Drawing, reading, fitness, blog writing, listening to music

#### **About**

I am a computer engineer who loves to work on Big Data and IOT. My dream is to work on developing groundbreaking ideas. I'm developing myself everyday for this. I am the person who believes on teamwork, likes to share knowledge and experience, enjoys creating and learning new things.

# **Career Summary**

# **Software Engineer**

#### Huawei

May 2022 to present

 Python and Java Software Development.

## **Full-Stack Developer**

Ne-Ka Elektronik Company February 2021 to May 2022

• Worked with PyQt5, ROS and Flask.

## **Computer Engineering Intern**

Mythology Tech Software R&D. Aug. 2020 to Sep. 2021

I wrote Android and IOS application that sends data using MQTT protocol. Using RabbitMQ Broker, I designed a desktop application that can run on localhost and connected it to my mobile applications.

### Web Development, Editorship

Gurme Soft Company Sep. 2019 to June. 2020

I have created an invoice plugin on Wordpress. I've done reviews about plugins and prepared videos on how to use them.

# **Computer Engineering Intern**

Orakçı Group of Companies Aug. 2019 to Sep. 2019

I wrote a service required for the company and did it with the python language. The service was sending a message celebrating the birthdays of the employees at the workplace every morning (If any birthday exists).

#### **Education**

## **Bursa Uludag University**

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering

- I finished my school with 3.31 GPA from 2017 to 2021.
- My graduation project was about "APPLICATION THAT CAN DISCRIMINATE RECYCLABLE SUBSTANCES".

## **Anadolu University**

Associate Degree Business Management Pr. Student

 Attending from Sept. 2020 to June 2022

# **Volunteering**

# Computer Society Committee Representative

IEEE BUU Student Branch April 2019 to August 2020

I organized code trainings, workshops, tea-talks and technical trips in the field of computers.

# **MERGEN Robotaxi Team Member**

IEEE BUU Student Branch Feb. 2020 to May 2021

I worked on object detection and the ROS system for the car. We were preparing for Teknofest.

# **IEEE BUU Otonomous Car Project**

IEEE BUU Student Branch June 2018 to Feb. 2020

I worked with the Park Detection team on object detection and parking algorithms. We worked for Marc-Autonomous Vehicle Competition.

## **Press and Media Representative**

IEEE BUU Student Branch Dec. 2017 to April 2019

- My job was designing social media posters of our club.
- Designer and author of BULUŞ Magazine.